

Dewa Raka Krisna Saputra

NFROMATICS COLLEGE STUDENT

Born in Surabaya, East Java on August 7th, 2001 and currently still live in said city.

Contact Details

Email: dewaraka90@gmail.com Phone: 085852943589 Socmed: dewarakaks

Profile

i'm a 20 years old infomatics college student with creative and motivated person who able work in team , willing to learn something new and able to work efficiently. interested in crew event, branding, social media, photography, fashion, coffee and cat.

Education History

SMA NEGERI 9 SURABAYA

2016 - 2019

S1 Informatics engineer, UPN Veteran Jawa Timur 2020 - Now Current GPA 3.89

Work Experience

ICE Agent 2018

November 2018

• Promoting event and selling ticket over 200+

Full Time Barista, Kopi Hagia

August 2019 - March 2020

Part Time Barista, Kopi Jiku

June 2021- Now

- Basic coffee knowledge manual and basic latte art.
- Able to operate coffee machine. Take customer orders and payment.
- Responsible for keeping the bar area stocked and clean.
- Accounting for sales and balancing drawers at the beginning and end of each shift.

Committee and Volunteer Experience

Commitee Pemira Himatifa 2021 at UPN Veteran Jawa TImur

Commitee for Student Orientation at Faculty Computer Science Pemaba 2021 Head Equipment Division

Committee for Student Orientation at Faculty Computer Science BCD 2021 Equipment Division

Commitee UKKH Welcome Party 2021 at UPN Veteran Jawa Timur

PDD Division

Commitee Fasilkom Gathering 2021

PDD Division

Volunteer Surabaya Marathon

Volunteer Tegur Sapa Music Festval

Skills and Characteristics

- Communication skills
- Marketing
- Creative Thinking
- Leadership and Teamwork
- Fast Learner

Programming Skills

- Phyton
- C